A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Projects, International Relations, RG 1.3, Series 155 FA388A
Rockefeller Archive Center
- International Relations, 1971-1989; 155
  - Columbia University: United States and Japanese Multilateral Diplomacy, 1980-1981, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 403)
  - Columbia University: United States and Japanese Multilateral Diplomacy: Evaluation, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 404)
  - Columbia University: United States and Japanese Multilateral Diplomacy: Supplementary Material (I), 1977-1978 (Box 36, Folder 405)
  - Columbia University: United States and Japanese Multilateral Diplomacy: Supplementary Material (II), 1978-1980, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 406)
  - Columbia University: United States and Japanese Multilateral Diplomacy: Supplementary Material (III), 1979 (Box 37, Folder 407)
  - Columbia University: United States and Japanese Multilateral Diplomacy: Supplementary Material (IV), 1979 (Box 37, Folder 408)
  - Columbia University: United States and Japanese Multilateral Diplomacy: Supplementary Material (V), 1979 (Box 37, Folder 409)
  - Columbia University: United States and Japanese Multilateral Diplomacy: Supplementary Material (VI), 1977 (Box 37, Folder 410)
  - Columbia University: United States and Japanese Multilateral Diplomacy: Supplementary Material (VII), 1977 (Box 37, Folder 411)
  - Columbia University: United States and Japanese Multilateral Diplomacy: Supplementary Material (VIII), 1977-1979 (Box 37, Folder 412)
  - Commission on U. S. Policy toward Africa: Front of File Material, 1977-1982, 1984-1985 (Box 37, Folder 413)
  - Commission on U. S. Policy toward Africa, 1977 February-June (Box 37, Folder 414)
  - Commission on U. S. Policy toward Africa, 1977 July-December (Box 37, Folder 415)
  - Commission on U. S. Policy toward Africa, 1978 February-June (Box 37, Folder 416)
  - Commission on U. S. Policy toward Africa, 1978 July-October (Box 37, Folder 417)
  - Commission on U. S. Policy toward Africa, 1978 November-December (Box 38, Folder 418)
  - Commission on U. S. Policy toward Africa, 1979 January-July (Box 38, Folder 419)
  - Commission on U. S. Policy toward Africa, 1979 August-November (Box 38, Folder 420)
  - Commission on U. S. Policy toward Africa, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 421)
  - Commission on U. S. Policy toward Africa, 1981 January-June (Box 38, Folder 422)
  - Commission on U. S. Policy toward Africa, 1981 July-December (Box 38, Folder 423)
  - Commission on U. S. Policy toward Africa, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 424)
  - Commission on U. S. Policy toward Africa, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 425)
  - Commission on U. S. Policy toward Africa, 1984-1986 (Box 38, Folder 426)
  - Commission on U. S. Policy toward Africa: Evaluation, 1978, 1985-1986 (Box 38, Folder 427)
  - Commission on U. S. Policy toward Africa: Supplementary Material (I), 1976 (Box 38, Folder 428)
  - Commission on U. S. Policy toward Africa: Supplementary Material (II), 1976 (Box 39, Folder 429)
  - Commission on U. S. Policy toward Africa: Supplementary Material (III), 1978 January (Box 39, Folder 430)
  - Commission on U. S. Policy toward Africa: Supplementary Material (IV), 1978 January (Box 39, Folder 431)
  - Commission on U. S. Policy toward Africa: Supplementary Material (V), 1978 February (Box 39, Folder 432)
  - Commission on U. S. Policy toward Africa: Supplementary Material (VI), 1978 February (Box 39, Folder 433)
  - Commission on U. S. Policy toward Africa: Supplementary Material (VII), 1983 (Box 39, Folder 434)
  - Commission on U. S. Policy toward Africa: Supplementary Material (VIII): Dissemination Report, 1981 June 29 (Box 39, Folder 435)
  - Commission on U. S. Policy toward Africa: Supplementary Material (IX): Dissemination Report (through Appendix A), 1981 December 31 (Box 39, Folder 436)
  - Commission on U. S. Policy toward Africa: Supplementary Material (X): Dissemination Report (Appendices B-D), 1981 December 31 (Box 39, Folder 437)
  - Commission on U. S. Policy toward Africa: Supplementary Material (XI): Dissemination Report (Appendix E), 1981 December 31 (Box 39, Folder 438)
  - Commission on U. S. Policy toward Africa: Supplementary Material (XII): Feasibility Study (through Appendix B), 1978 August 24 (Box 39, Folder 439)
  - Commission on U. S. Policy toward Africa: Supplementary Material (XIII): Feasibility Study (Appendices C-I), 1978 August 24 (Box 39, Folder 440)
  - Commission on U. S. Policy toward Africa: Supplementary Material (XIV): Feasibility Study (Appendix J), 1978 August 24 (Box 39, Folder 441)
  - Commission on U. S. Policy toward Africa: Supplementary Material (XV): Feasibility Study (Appendices K-N), 1978 August 24 (Box 40, Folder 442)
  - Commission on U. S. Policy toward Africa: Supplementary Material (XVI): Report Analysis (Sections I-III, Appendix A), 1978 October 4 (Box 40, Folder 443)
  - Commission on U. S. Policy toward Africa: Supplementary Material (XVII): Report Analysis (Appendix B1-7), 1978 October 4 (Box 40, Folder 444)
  - Commission on U. S. Policy toward Africa: Supplementary Material (XVIII): Report Analysis (Appendix B8), 1978 October 4 (Box 40, Folder 445)
  - Commission on U. S. Policy toward Africa: Supplementary Material (XIX): Report Analysis (Appendices B9-D), 1978 October 4 (Box 40, Folder 446)
  - Commission on U. S. Policy toward Africa: Supplementary Material (XX): Report Analysis (Sections I-III, Appendices A-B3), 1978 October 20 (Box 40, Folder 447)
  - Commission on U. S. Policy toward Africa: Supplementary Material (XXI): Report Analysis (Appendix B4-7), 1978 October 20 (Box 40, Folder 448)
  - Commission on U. S. Policy toward Africa: Supplementary Material (XXII): Report Analysis (Appendix B8), 1978 October 20 (Box 40, Folder 449)
  - Commission on U. S. Policy toward Africa: Supplementary Material (XXIII): Report Analysis (Appendices B9-D), 1978 October 20 (Box 40, Folder 450)
  - Committee for Economic Development: Mexico-U.S. Business Leaders Conference, 1983-1985 (Box 40, Folder 451)
  - Committee for Economic Development: U. S.-Japanese Conference, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 452)
  - Committee for Economic Development: U. S.-Japanese Conference, 1980-1982 (Box 40, Folder 453)
  - Committee for National Security: U. S.-Soviet Relations Conference, 1983-1984 (Box 41, Folder 454)
  - Committee for National Security: Women and National Security Conference, 1982 February-March (Box 41, Folder 455)
  - Committee for National Security: Women and National Security Conference, 1982 April-1983, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 456)
  - Committee for National Security: Women and National Security Conference: Supplementary Material, 1981-1982 (Box 41, Folder 457)
  - Committee for National Security: Women Leaders Conference, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 458)
  - Consultative Group on International Economic and Monetary Affairs: Front of File Material (I) (Minutes), 1978-1984 (Box 41, Folder 459)
  - Consultative Group on International Economic and Monetary Affairs: Front of File Material (II), 1979-1982 (Box 41, Folder 460)
  - Consultative Group on International Economic and Monetary Affairs: Front of File Material (III), 1983-1984, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 461)
  - Consultative Group on International Economic and Monetary Affairs, 1978 January-April (Box 41, Folder 462)
  - Consultative Group on International Economic and Monetary Affairs, 1978 May (Box 41, Folder 463)
  - Consultative Group on International Economic and Monetary Affairs, 1978 June (Box 41, Folder 464)
  - Consultative Group on International Economic and Monetary Affairs, 1978 July-August (Box 42, Folder 465)
  - Consultative Group on International Economic and Monetary Affairs, 1978 September (Box 42, Folder 466)
  - Consultative Group on International Economic and Monetary Affairs, 1978 October-November (Box 42, Folder 467)
  - Consultative Group on International Economic and Monetary Affairs, 1978 December (Box 42, Folder 468)
  - Consultative Group on International Economic and Monetary Affairs, 1979 January-May (Box 42, Folder 469)
  - Consultative Group on International Economic and Monetary Affairs, 1979 June-December (Box 42, Folder 470)
  - Consultative Group on International Economic and Monetary Affairs, 1980 January-February (Box 42, Folder 471)
  - Consultative Group on International Economic and Monetary Affairs, 1980 June-December (Box 42, Folder 472)
  - Consultative Group on International Economic and Monetary Affairs, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 473)
  - Consultative Group on International Economic and Monetary Affairs, 1982 (Box 43, Folder 474)
  - Consultative Group on International Economic and Monetary Affairs, 1983 January-March (Box 43, Folder 475)
  - Consultative Group on International Economic and Monetary Affairs, 1983 April-August (Box 43, Folder 476)
  - Consultative Group on International Economic and Monetary Affairs, 1983 September-November (Box 43, Folder 477)
  - Consultative Group on International Economic and Monetary Affairs, 1983 December (Box 43, Folder 478)
  - Consultative Group on International Economic and Monetary Affairs, 1984 January-March (Box 43, Folder 479)
  - Consultative Group on International Economic and Monetary Affairs, 1984 April-October (Box 43, Folder 480)
  - Consultative Group on International Economic and Monetary Affairs, 1985 January (Box 43, Folder 481)
  - Consultative Group on International Economic and Monetary Affairs, 1985 May-December (Box 43, Folder 482)
  - Consultative Group on International Economic and Monetary Affairs, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 483)
  - Consultative Group on International Economic and Monetary Affairs: Supplementary Material (I), 1979 (Box 43, Folder 484)
  - Consultative Group on International Economic and Monetary Affairs: Supplementary Material (II), 1979 (Box 44, Folder 485)
  - Consultative Group on International Economic and Monetary Affairs: Supplementary Material (III), 1979 (Box 44, Folder 486)
  - Consultative Group on International Economic and Monetary Affairs: Supplementary Material (IV), 1979 (Box 44, Folder 487)
  - Consultative Group on International Economic and Monetary Affairs: Supplementary Material (V), 1979 (Box 44, Folder 488)
  - Consultative Group on International Economic and Monetary Affairs: Supplementary Material (VI), 1979 (Box 44, Folder 489)
  - Consultative Group on International Economic and Monetary Affairs: Supplementary Material (VII), 1979 (Box 44, Folder 490)
  - Consultative Group on International Economic and Monetary Affairs: Supplementary Material (VIII), 1979 (Box 44, Folder 491)
  - Consultative Group on International Economic and Monetary Affairs: Supplementary Material (IX), 1980 (Box 44, Folder 492)
  - Consultative Group on International Economic and Monetary Affairs: Supplementary Material (X), 1984 November 30 (Box 44, Folder 493)
  - Consultative Group on International Economic and Monetary Affairs: Supplementary Material (XI), 1985 (Box 44, Folder 494)
  - Consultative Group on International Economic and Monetary Affairs: Supplementary Material (XII): Mailing Lists (I), no date (Box 44, Folder 495)
  - Consultative Group on International Economic and Monetary Affairs: Supplementary Material (XIII): Mailing Lists (II), no date (Box 44, Folder 496)
  - Consultative Group on International Economic and Monetary Affairs: Supplementary Material (XIV): Press Coverage (I), 1978-1979, 1981-1982 (Box 44, Folder 497)
  - Consultative Group on International Economic and Monetary Affairs: Supplementary Material (XV): Press Coverage (II), 1980, 1983 (Box 44, Folder 498)
  - Consultative Group on International Economic and Monetary Affairs: Supplementary Material (XVI): Publications (34 pieces), 1980-1984, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 499)
  - Consultative Group on International Economic and Monetary Affairs: Energy Study Group, 1980-1981 (Box 46, Folder 500)
  - Wayne A. Cornelius, 1978-1979, 1982-1983 (Box 46, Folder 501)
  - Wayne A. Cornelius: Supplementary Material (I): "Mexican Migration to the United States", pp. 1-192, 1979 May (Box 46, Folder 502)
  - Wayne A. Cornelius: Supplementary Material (II): "Mexican Migration to the United States", pp. 193-307, 1979 May (Box 46, Folder 503)
  - Wayne A. Cornelius: Supplementary Material (III), 1979 May (Box 46, Folder 504)
  - Wayne A. Cornelius: Supplementary Material (IV), 1981 (Box 46, Folder 505)
  - Wayne A. Cornelius: Supplementary Material (V), 1981 (Box 46, Folder 506)
  - Cornell University: Energy Conference (I), 1975-1976, 1978, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 507)
  - Cornell University: Energy Conference (II), 1975-1979, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 508)
  - Cornell University: Military Research, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 509)
  - Cornell University: Military Research, 1976 January-June (Box 46, Folder 510)
  - Cornell University: Military Research, 1976 July (Box 46, Folder 511)
  - Cornell University: Military Research, 1976 August-1977 June (Box 47, Folder 512)
  - Cornell University: Military Research, 1977 July-December (Box 47, Folder 513)
  - Cornell University: Military Research, 1978 (Box 47, Folder 514)
  - Cornell University: Military Research, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 515)
  - Cornell University: Military Research: Supplementary Material, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 516)
  - Cornell University: Warsaw Pact Conference, 1981-1982 (Box 47, Folder 517)
  - Cornell University: Warsaw Pact Conference, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 518)
  - Council for the United States and Italy: Conference, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 519)
  - Council for the United States and Italy: Conference, 1984-1985 February (Box 47, Folder 520)
  - Council for the United States and Italy: Conference, 1985 March-April (Box 47, Folder 521)
  - (489) – Council of Unions of South Africa: Working Women, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 522)
  - (489) – Council of Unions of South Africa: Working Women, 1983 (Box 48, Folder 523)
  - (489) – Council of Unions of South Africa: Working Women, 1984-1985 September (Box 48, Folder 524)
  - (489) – Council of Unions of South Africa: Working Women, 1985 October-1986 August (Box 48, Folder 525)
  - (489) – Council of Unions of South Africa: Working Women, 1986 September-1987 (Box 48, Folder 526)
  - Council on Foreign Relations: Africa Project, 1978, 1980-1981 (Box 48, Folder 527)
  - Council on Foreign Relations: Africa Project: Evaluation, 1981-1984 (Box 48, Folder 528)
  - Council on Foreign Relations: Africa Project: Supplementary Material (I): "Africa and the United States", through Chapter 3, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 529)
  - Council on Foreign Relations: Africa Project: Supplementary Material (II): "Africa and the United States", Chapters 4-7, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 530)
  - Council on Foreign Relations: Africa Project: Supplementary Material (III), 1980 (Box 48, Folder 531)
  - Council on Foreign Relations: Africa Project: Supplementary Material (IV), 1980 (Box 49, Folder 532)
  - Council on Foreign Relations: Africa Project: Supplementary Material (V), 1980 (Box 49, Folder 533)
  - Council on Foreign Relations: Africa Project: Supplementary Material (VI), 1980 (Box 49, Folder 534)
  - Council on Foreign Relations: African Development, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 535)
  - Council on Foreign Relations: African Development, 1985-1986 March (Box 49, Folder 536)
  - Council on Foreign Relations: African Development, 1986 April-November, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 537)
  - Council on Foreign Relations: European Communism, 1976-1979 (Box 49, Folder 538)
  - Council on Foreign Relations: European Communism: Evaluation, 1982-1983 (Box 49, Folder 539)
  - Council on Foreign Relations: 1980's Project (I), 1974, 1976-1978, 1980-1981 (Box 49, Folder 540)
  - Council on Foreign Relations: 1980's Project (II), 1973 (Box 49, Folder 541)
  - Council on Foreign Relations: 1980's Project (II), 1974 February-April (Box 49, Folder 542)
  - Council on Foreign Relations: 1980's Project (II), 1974 May-1975 (Box 50, Folder 543)
  - Council on Foreign Relations: 1980's Project (II), 1976 (Box 50, Folder 544)
  - Council on Foreign Relations: 1980's Project (II), 1977 (Box 50, Folder 545)
  - Council on Foreign Relations: 1980's Project (II), 1978 (Box 50, Folder 546)
  - Council on Foreign Relations: 1980's Project (II), 1979, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 547)
  - Council on Foreign Relations: 1980's Project: Evaluation, 1981-1983 (Box 50, Folder 548)
  - Council on Foreign Relations: 1980's Project: Supplementary Material (I): Enclosures 1-5, 1974 February 15 (Box 50, Folder 549)
  - Council on Foreign Relations: 1980's Project: Supplementary Material (II): Appendix, 1974 February 15 (Box 50, Folder 550)
  - Council on Foreign Relations: 1980's Project: Supplementary Material (III), 1975-1976 (Box 50, Folder 551)
  - Council on Foreign Relations: 1980's Project: Supplementary Material (IV), 1976 October 14 (Box 50, Folder 552)
  - Council on Foreign Relations: 1980's Project: Supplementary Material (V), 1977-1978 (Box 51, Folder 553)
  - Council on Foreign Relations: 1980's Project: Supplementary Material (VI): Status Report, 1975 September (Box 51, Folder 554)
  - Council on Foreign Relations: 1980's Project: Supplementary Material (VII): Status Report - Appendices, 1975 September (Box 51, Folder 555)
  - Council on Foreign Relations: 1980's Project: Supplementary Material (VIII): Status Report, Parts I-IV C, 1976 October (Box 51, Folder 556)
  - Council on Foreign Relations: 1980's Project: Supplementary Material (IX): Status Report, Parts IV D-IX G, 1976 October (Box 51, Folder 557)
  - Council on Foreign Relations: 1980's Project: Supplementary Material (X): Status Report, Parts IV H-VII, 1976 October (Box 51, Folder 558)
  - Council on Foreign Relations: Soviet-American Relations, 1979, 1982, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 559)
  - Council on Foundations, Inc.: International Grantmaking, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 560)
  - Council on Foundations, Inc.: International Grantmaking, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 561)
  - Council on Foundations, Inc.: International Grantmaking, 1983, 1985, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 562)
  - Ashok V. Desai, 1979-1980 (Box 52, Folder 563)
  - Ashok V. Desai, 1980 February (Box 52, Folder 564)
  - Ashok V. Desai, 1980 March (Box 52, Folder 565)
  - Ashok V. Desai, 1980 May-November (Box 52, Folder 566)
  - (489) – Diakonia: Durban Detainees Support Committee (DESCOM), 1985-1987, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 567)
  - Emory University: Carter Center: Middle East Program, 1983 April-September (Box 52, Folder 568)
  - Emory University: Carter Center: Middle East Program, 1983 October-1984 (Box 52, Folder 569)
  - Emory University: Carter Center: Middle East Program: Supplementary Material (I): Middle East Consultation Program Materials (I), 1983 November (Box 52, Folder 570)
  - Emory University: Carter Center: Middle East Program: Supplementary Material (II): Middle East Consultation Program Materials (II), 1983 November (Box 52, Folder 571)
  - Emory University: Carter Center: Middle East Program: Supplementary Material (III), 1983 November (Box 52, Folder 572)
  - Energy Economics Educational Foundation: Conference Proceedings: Front of File Material, 1981, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 573)
  - Energy Economics Educational Foundation: Conference Proceedings, 1979, 1981-1982 (Box 53, Folder 574)
  - Energy Economics Educational Foundation: Conference Proceedings: Supplementary Material, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 575)
  - Energy Policy, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 576)
  - Energy Policy, 1978 January-February (Box 53, Folder 577)
  - Energy Policy, 1978 March (Box 53, Folder 578)
  - Energy Policy, 1978 April-November (Box 53, Folder 579)
  - Energy Policy, 1979 February-March (Box 53, Folder 580)
  - Energy Policy, 1979 April-August (Box 53, Folder 581)
  - Energy Policy, 1979 October-November (Box 53, Folder 582)
  - Energy Policy, 1980-1982 (Box 53, Folder 583)
  - Energy Policy: Evaluation, 1980-1981 (Box 53, Folder 584)
  - Energy Policy: Supplementary Material (I), 1978 (Box 54, Folder 585)
  - Energy Policy: Supplementary Material (II), 1978 (Box 54, Folder 586)
  - Energy Problems: Conference, 1980-1982 (Box 54, Folder 587)
  - Richard R. Fagen, 1977-1978 May (Box 54, Folder 588)
  - Richard R. Fagen, 1978 June-November (Box 54, Folder 589)
  - Richard R. Fagen, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 590)
  - Richard R. Fagen, 1980, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 591)
  - (489) – Federated Union of Black Arts: Development Office, 1982, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 592)
  - (489) – Federated Union of Black Arts: Development Office, 1986-1987, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 593)
  - Florida International University: Honduras Conference, 1984 February-August (Box 54, Folder 594)
  - Florida International University: Honduras Conference, 1984 November (Box 54, Folder 595)
  - Florida International University: Honduras Conference, 1984 December-1987 (Box 55, Folder 596)
  - Florida International University: Honduras Conference: Supplementary Material (I), 1983 (Box 55, Folder 597)
  - Florida International University: Honduras Conference: Supplementary Material (II), 1983-1984 (Box 55, Folder 598)
  - Florida International University: Honduras Conference: Supplementary Material (III), 1983-1984 (Box 55, Folder 599)
  - Foreign Policy Research Institute: Soviet-American Conference, 1980 April-July (Box 55, Folder 600)
  - Foreign Policy Research Institute: Soviet-American Conference, 1980 December-1981 (Box 55, Folder 601)
  - Foreign Policy Research Institute: Soviet-American Conference, 1982-1984 (Box 55, Folder 602)
  - French Institute of International Relations: Middle East, 1983-1985 (Box 55, Folder 603)
  - French Institute of International Relations: World Economy, 1983 (Box 55, Folder 604)
  - French Institute of International Relations: World Economy, 1984 July (Box 55, Folder 605)
  - French Institute of International Relations: World Economy, 1984 September-1986, 1992 (Box 55, Folder 606)
  - French Institute of International Relations: World Economy: Supplementary Material, 1985-1986 (Box 55, Folder 607)
  - David S. Fries, 1984-1985 (Box 55, Folder 608)
  - Georgetown University: Soviet Strategy in Latin America, 1982 April (Box 56, Folder 609)
  - Georgetown University: Soviet Strategy in Latin America, 1982 May-1983 (Box 56, Folder 610)
  - Georgetown University: Soviet Strategy in Latin America: Supplementary Material (I), 1982 (Box 56, Folder 611)
  - Georgetown University: Soviet Strategy in Latin America: Supplementary Material (II), 1983 (Box 56, Folder 612)
  - Georgetown University: U. S. Security and the Third World, 1980-1982 (Box 56, Folder 613)
  - Georgetown University: U. S. Security Review, 1982-1983 (Box 56, Folder 614)
  - Georgetown University: U. S. Security Review, 1984 February-May (Box 56, Folder 615)
  - Georgetown University: U. S. Security Review, 1984 June-1986 (Box 56, Folder 616)
  - Georgetown University: U. S. Security Review: Supplementary Material (I), 1982, 1985 (Box 56, Folder 617)
  - Georgetown University: U. S. Security Review: Supplementary Material (II), 1985 (Box 56, Folder 618)
  - German Marshall Fund: International Trade Conferences, 1980-1981 (Box 56, Folder 619)
  - (489) – Grassroots Publications: Media Training, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 620)
  - (489) – Grassroots Publications: Media Training, 1985-1986 (Box 57, Folder 621)
  - (489) – Grassroots Publications: Media Training, 1987-1989 (Box 57, Folder 622)
  - (489) – Grassroots Publications: Media Training: Supplementary Material (I), 1984 (Box 57, Folder 623)
  - (489) – Grassroots Publications: Media Training: Supplementary Material (II), 1985, no date (Box 57, Folder 624)
  - (489) – Grassroots Publications: Media Training: Supplementary Material (III), 1985-1986, no date (Box 57, Folder 625)
  - (489) – Grassroots Publications: Newspaper "Learning Roots", 1986-1988 February 8 (Box 57, Folder 626)
  - (489) – Grassroots Publications: Newspaper "Learning Roots", 1988 February 15-August (Box 57, Folder 627)
  - (489) – Grassroots Publications: Newspaper "Learning Roots": Supplementary Material, 1985-1986, 1988 (Box 57, Folder 628)